Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
- Star Theatre
  - A Night at Steve Brodie's, January 31, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Steve Brodie Comedy Company; Overture - W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Coakley and Heusted; Hiatt and Pearl; Lancaster and Collins; Leslie and Curdy; C. W. Williams; Miss Annie Hart; "A Night at Steve Brodie's"; and others.
  - The Peep-O'-Day Club, February 7, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Sam Devere's Own Company in "The Peep-O'-Day Club" with Mildred Howard De Grey; W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Rice Brothers; Pearl Haight; Byron and Langdon; Miss Kathryn Rowe Palmer; Bartell and Morris; and others.
  - Flynn & Sheridan Big Sensation Double Show, February 28, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Flynn & Sheridan Big Sensation Double Show; W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Mlle. Zittella; Miss May Bohee; Gordon and Hughes; Marion and Pearl; Bohee and Coates; Lina and Vani; Burlesques, and others.
  - A Night on Broadway, March 21, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Weber's Parisian Widows; Raymond and Clarke; Lizzie Van; The Cosmoplitan Trio; Burman Sisters; Tenley and Simonds; Howard and Emerson; Boyce and Black; the burlesque, "A Night On Broadway"; and more.
  - A Trip Across The Ocean, March 28, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W.F. Daniel and Orchestra; John L. Sullivan's Comedy and Big Vaudeville Company in "A Trip Across The Ocean"; The Brownings; Petching Brothers; Miss Emma Carus; The Great Darmondy; Detty and Murray; Begley and Lee; and others.
  - The Countryman's Dream, April 11, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; T.E. Miaco's City Club Company; "Madame May's First Night;" Miss Mattie Cope; Conroy and McFarland; Mr. Lew Palmer; Bert Leslie and Carrie Fulton; "The Countryman's Dream," a musical burlesque; and more.
  - Bunco Bike, April 25, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Bryant & Watson's American Burlesquers; "The Hebrew Charity Ball"; Mitchell and Love; Clarice Sisters; Washburn Sisters; "Bunco Bike" with Harry C. Bryant et al; and more.
  - A World of Pleasure, May 2, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Rentz-Santley Novelty and Burlesque Co.; the burlesque, "A World of Pleasure." Book by Charles Lovenburg. With Lottie Elliott, Violet Barney, Miss Tyrene, Lillie Engstrom et al.
  - Café D'La Amerique, May 30, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Rose Sydell's London Belles in "Café D'La Amerique"; Edgar Bixley; Winnifred Stewart; Sydell and St. Clair; Campbell and Shepp; The Extravaganza, by W.S. Campbell, "Isle of Sham-Pain"; and more.
  - 30 Minutes At Monte Carlo, June 6, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; The Monte Carlo Girls in "30 Minutes At Monte Carlo"; "The Vassar Girls"; Swinson Sisters; W.B. Watson, assisted by Jeanette Dupre, in "I'm So Loose"; Eva Swinburne; Ward and Brown; Fred Roberts; and more.
  - Robin Hood, Jr. Burlesquers, June 13, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: W. F. Daniel and Orchestra; Robin Hood, Jr. Burlesquers; "Lord Cork's Reception" with Helen Russell, Ruby Leoni et al; Russell and Wells; Herbert Brothers; McCabe and Sabine; Clements and Marshall in "The New Patient"; and more.
  - A Summer's Outing, August 15, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: The London Gaiety Girls; "A Summer's Outing," a musical burlesque, by Percy Gaunt, with Tot Guichard et al; Harry Burgoyne; McAvoy and Gilson; Mlle. Oceana; Gus Mills; Bijou Comedy Trio; and more.
  - Darktown Outing at Blackville Park, May 16, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: John W. Isham's Famous Original Octoroons; W.F. Daniels and Orchestra; "Darktown Outing at Blackville Park" with George Williams, Walter Smart et al; Miss Madah Hyer; Mallory Brothers; Miss Kittie Carter; and others.
  - Slumming, September 5, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Hurtig & Seamon's Bowery Burlesquers; Nelson Sisters; Lewis and Elliott; Gladys Van; Gracey and Burnette; Truly Shattuck; The World's Trio; "Slumming." Book by Loney Haskell.
  - Pousse Café, September 12, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; "Pousse Café," book by Edgar Smith, with Frederic Hallen et al; Dailey and Hilton; Thomas O'Brien; Mamie Gehrue; Hallen and Fuller; and others.
  - Joke in High Life, September 19, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; "Joke in High Life" by John V. Brice; Bohee and Hammond; Nunn and Bradford; Bryce and Inman; The Daughters of Columbia; Lina and Vani; Blocksom and Burns; and others.
  - A Night at the Armory, Novmeber 14, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Irwin Brothers' Burlesquers; Thompson and Carter; Sidney and Von Tilzer; Scott and Wilson; Street Arabs Quartette; Carver and Black; "A Night at the Armory," Book by W. L. Ballauf; and more.
  - Weber's Dainty Duchess Co, November 21, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Weber's Dainty Duchess Co.; Raymond and Clarke; Montague and West; Aleene and La Rue; The Mimic Four; Hayes and Bandy; Burke Brothers; Kessler and Carrick; "Dainty Duchess" with Charles H. Burke et al.
  - A Fountain of Pleasure, November 28, 1898 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Fred Rider's Moulin Rouge Extravaganza, "A Fountain of Pleasure." With Nellie Walters, Norma Wills, Charles Harris, Monte Collins, James Cooper, Harry Stewart, Nettie Batchelor, Lillian Belmont et al.
  - Sam Devere's Own Company, January 9, 1899 (Box 3)
    Performances: Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Sam Devere's Own Company; Jones and Sutton; Herbert Ashley; Coakley and Huested; O'Brien and Buckley; Fanchonette Sisters; Barnes and Sisson; Walter J. Talbot; "The Peep-O'-Day Club;" and more.
  - Sheridan & Faust's Metropolitan Burlesquers, January 30, 1899 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Sheridan & Faust's Metropolitan Burlesquers: Grand Opening Pageant, "Re-union of Nations"; Curtis and Wooley; Lucier and Belle; Weston and Beasley; Madame Flower; and more.
  - Phil Sheridan's New City Sports Big Show, May 15, 1899 (Box 3)
    Phil Sheridan's New City Sports Big Show; Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; "Maloney's Visit; or, An Old Maid's Dilemma," by Phil Sheridan; Alice Leslie; Farum and Nelson; Scanlon and Stevens; Miss Crissie Sheridan and 12 Lovely Flowers; and more.
  - The Female Rounders, October 2, 1899 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Sam Devere's Own Co. in "The Female Rounders." By Billy O'Brien. With Billy O'Brien, Mike Murphy, Walter Talbot, Ed Rentz, Lew Buckley, James Cunningham, Leo Edwards et al.
  - Reilly and Wood's Big Show, October 9, 1899 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Reilly and Wood's Big Show: Jennings and Alto; Meeker-Baker Trio; Pat Reilly; The Misses Hanson and Nelson; the comedy, "One Flight Down," headed by Pat Reilly; and more.
  - The New Broadway Burlesquers, March 12, 1900 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; The New Broadway Burlesquers: Carlin Sisters; Lew Wells; Emma Carus; Gilbert and Goldie; McAvoy and May; Frobel and Ruge; "On the Bench"; and more.
  - A Tin Wedding, March 26, 1900 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Weber's Parisian Widows: Leonard and Bernard; Russell and Tillyne; Ruby Marion; Bartell and Morris; Manhattan Comedy Four; Howard and Bland; "A Tin Wedding" by Al. Shean; and more.
  - Miner & Van's Bohemian Burlesquers, September 16, 1901 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Miner & Van's Bohemian Burlesquers: "U. S. Cruiser 'Bohemia,'" by George Totten Smith; St. John and Nicolai; Riley and Hughes; Barr and Evans; Maddox and Wayne; and others.
  - The Brigadiers, September 30, 1901 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; The Brigadiers; Lida Dexter and Company in "A Modern Diana"; Miss Carrie Thomas; "The Vanishing Brigadiers"; McDonald Brothers; The Fete of the Gondoliers; and others.
  - A Day At West Point, or, All Is Fair in Love or War, November 25, 1901 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Weber's Parisian Widows; Nelson and Milledge; Miss Mildred Murray; Snyder and Buckley; Garrity Sisters; Nevarros; "A Day At West Point; or, All Is Fair in Love or War." Book by Snyder and Buckley; and more.
  - The Vaudeville Craze, January 27, 1901 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; M. M. Theise's Own Company in "The Vaudeville Craze." An Original Creation by M. M. Theise. Staged by Phil Gotthold. With E. M. Gallagher, J. J. Barrett et al. Plus more vaudeville acts.
  - The Cloak Models, February 10, 1902 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Sam Devere's Own Company of Star Artists: Hodge, Heyward and Lancaster; Phasey Troupe; Royal Ascot Girls; Marion and Vedder; The Troubador Four; performance of "The Cloak Models"; and more.
  - The Reception of Count O'Fudge, March 31, 1902 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Al. Reeves Famous Big Company in "The Reception of Count O'Fudge." Book by Chas. Hoey. Performances conclude with "A Night at Narragansett Pier." Book and Ensembles by Charles Sabine.
  - On a Sleeper, August 16, 1902 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; The Bowery Burlesquers. "On A Sleeper," by Willard Holcombe; More performances by: Gilbert and Goldie; Farrell-Taylor Trio; Barrows; The Eretto Family; "Slumming" by Loney Haskell.
  - Trans-Atlantic Burlesquers, November 3, 1902 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Trans-Atlantic Burlesquers. Performances by: Anna Conrad and Company; Bulla and Raymond; Dunbar Sisters; Bickel and Watson; Ed. Lee Wrothe and Jno. J. McCowan; and "On the Yu-Con."
  - A Day and A Night, April 4, 1904 (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra; Dainty Duchess Company in "A Day and A Night," written, staged and produced by Williams and Adams. Also Idylla Vyner; Walthour and Kreamer; Williams and Adams; Zimmer; "The Festive Throng."
  - The Dollar Line, February 20, 1905 (Box 3)
    Louis Doll, Musical Director. Sam Devere's Own Company in the Musical Farce Comedy, "The Dollar Line." Other vaudeville performances to follow by: Gertie LeClair; Shrodes; The Exposition Four; and others.
  - In the Tenderloin, February 27, 1905 (Box 3)
    Louis Doll, Musical Director. The New Majestics in the Musical Satire, "In the Tenderloin." Other vaudeville performances to follow by: Harvey and Walker; Anderson and Wallace; The Sisters Bellatzer; Farron and Fay; and others.
  - A Misfit Family, May 8, 1905 (Box 3)
    Louis Doll, Musical Director. Charles H. Waldron's Trocadero Burlesquers in the Musical Comedy, "A Misfit Family." By Harry Montague. Other vaudeville performances to follow by: William Bartell; The Grahams; Meehan's Comedy Dogs; and others.
  - Fads and Follies, January 15, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Performances: Harry and Eva La Reane; Lawson and Namon; Harris and Walters; Mike S. Whallen; The Great Darmody; John and Harry Dillon; "Fads and Follies, Or, A Night on the Boulevard."
  - McNulty and the Model, January 16, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Performances: The Gay Masqueraders in "McNulty and the Model." Other vaudeville performances to follow by: Prof. Nick Brown, assisted by Lyda Camille; Bud Snyder; Electric Clark Sisters; The Murphys; and others.
  - The Typewriter's Wedding-Day, January 23, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Australian Beauties in "The Typewriter's Wedding-Day." Written by Frank Dumont. With Slim Williams; John Sheehan; Tony Kennedy; Smith O'Brien et al; Other vaudeville performances to follow.
  - An Alderman's Election, February 6, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Clark Brothers' Royal Burlesquers. Performances: Sisters Bernard; The Cosmoplitan Trio; Annie Morris; Howard and Emerson; "An Alderman's Election," written by Howard and Emerson; and more.
  - A Parisian Night, February 13, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Ed. F. Rush's Famous Bon-Ton Burlesquers in "A Parisian Night." Other vaudeville performances to follow by: Miss Agnes Behler; Forman and West; Morrison and Markey; "A Devil of a Time," by Ned Monroe; and more.
  - A Dainty Duchess, February 20, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Weber's Dainty Duchess Co.: Raymond and Clarke; Clerise Sisters; The Mimic Four; Aleene and La Rue; Hayes and Bandy; Burke Brothers; Kessler and Carrick; "A Dainty Duchess."
  - Red Birds at the Seashore, March 6, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Sam A. Scribner's Gay Morning Glories Vaudevillers and Burlesquers; Grant and Grant; Willis and Barron; Smith and Fuller; McPhee and Hill; "Red Birds at the Seashore," written by W. H. Miles; and others.
  - Gay Monte Carlo, March 13, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. The Broadway Burlesquers; Merritt and Rozella; Mitchell Sisters; Harry Le Clair; Smith and Cook; Lottie Gilson; Bennett and Rich; "Gay Monte Carlo," book by Dave Lewis; and more.
  - Mixed Ale, March 20, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Robie & Dinkins' Knickerbocker Burlesquers; Raymond and West; Grant and Durand; Shayne and Worden; The Three Gardners; Mike S. Whallen; Wright Sisters; the Farcical Burlesque, "Mixed Ale"; and more.
  - A Scrambled Egg, March 27, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Miner & Van's Bohemian Burlesquers. Performances: Fisher and Jansen; Myrtle Tressider; Saxon and Brooke; Evans and Vidocq; Van and Nobriga; the Comedy, "A Scrambled Egg"; and more.
  - Training the Lambs, April 10, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Harry Morris' Little Lambs in "Training the Lambs." Other vaudeville performances by: Charles Kenna; The Johnson Trio; Jean Cunningham; Dilks and Wade; Fanchon Sisters; Cook and Sonora; "General Fink's Army."
  - Trans-Atlantic Burlesquers, April 14, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Trans-Atlantic Burlesquers; Dayton Sisters; Etta Victoria; Wrothe and Wakefield; Three Sisters Dunbar; Bickel and Watson.
  - Fads and Follies, April 30, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. "Fads and Follies, Or, A Night on the Boulevard"; Harry and Eva La Reane; Whallen and Du Pree; Harris and Walters; The Great Darmody; The Famous World's Trio.
  - Barnstorming, August 26, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Rose Sydell's New London Belles Big Show in "Barnstorming," a One-Act Farce. Also: Lillie Roberts; Wheeler and Vedder; Ruth Denver and Company; Hafford and Worth; The Marvelous Dunhams; James A. La Clare; and others.
  - An Irishman's Visit to Paris, September 9, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Phil Sheridan's New City Sports. "An Irishman's Visit to Paris"; Robinson and Speck; Blodgett Sisters; Craig and Ardell; Grovini and Murray; "Thirty Minutes of Trouble, Or, A Hot Night in a Buffalo Hotel"; and more.
  - The Husband's Return, September 26, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Reilly & Wood's Big Show; The Cyclonic Six in "The Husband's Return"; Pat Reilly; The De Filippis; Dunbar Sisters; The Three Mortons; The Weston Sisters; Baker and Reynolds; Bessie Lamb; and others.
  - Raz-Ma-Taz, October 14, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Weber's Dainty Duchess; Milton and Maude Wood; Bryce and Inman in "Two Jolly Companions"; Australian Twin Andersons; The Exposition Four; Huntings; Allan Wightman; the burletta, in One-Act, "Raz-Ma-Taz."
  - Mum, October 17, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Fred Rider's New Night Owls in "Mum," a Comedy-Farce Burlesque written by Wiley Hamilton. With May Clark Van Osten, Florence Wragland, Violet St. Clair, Wiley Hamilton, G. Clayton Frye et al.
  - Red Birds at the Seashore, October 24, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Sam A. Scribner's Gay Morning Glories Vaudevillers and Burlesquers; Grant and Grant; Madeline Franks; Wills and Barron; McCabe and Sabine; McPhee and Hill; "Red Birds at the Seashore," by W. H. Miles; and more.
  - Fads and Follies, October 28, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Fads and Follies Burlesquers; Clifford and Hall; Effie Brooklyn; Post and Clinton; Mosher, Houghton and Mosher; Gertie DeMilt; The Musical Bells; Eddie Girard and Company; and "Fads and Follies."
  - A Night on Broadway, October 31, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. Weber's Parisian Widow's. Dryden and Leslie; Burman Sisters; Gilbert and Goldie; Cushman and Holcombe; Manhattan Comedy Four; Boyce and Black; the burlesque "A Night on Broadway." Book and Music by Harry B. Marshall.
  - Broadway Burlesquers on Broadway, December 9, [no year] (Box 3)
    Emilio Donofrio and Orchestra. The Broadway Burlesquers, Max Spiegel: Manager. Performances: The Murphys; The Original Rio Bros.; Rosalie; Kelly and Davis; Frederick Bros. and Burns; Le Roy and Woodford; the finale, "Broadway Burlesquers on Broadway."
- Strand
  - Casey at the Bat, May 7, 1927 (Box 3)
    1. Overture; 2. A Tribute to Mother; 3. Harry Breuer; 4. Mark Strand Topical Review; 5. The Moth and the Flame, featuring Vlasta Maslova; 6. The Happiness Boys; 7. "Casey at the Bat" with Wallace Beery et al. A Paramount Picture.
- Sumner
  - Unfinished Business, November 16-22, [1941] (Box 3)
    Films: "Unfinished Business" with Irene Dunne, Robert Montgomery; "The Smiling Ghost" with Wayne Morris; "Aloma of the Seas" with Dorothy Lamour; "Badlands of Dakota" with Robert Stack.
- Throop Theatre
  - The Photo-Drama of Creation, [November 20, 1915] (Box 3)
    The Divine Plan as seen by Pastor Russell. Free Motion Pictures, "The Photo-Drama of Creation." Four parts, two hours each.
- Tivoli Theatre
  - The Wrong Mr. Wright, February 8, [1927] (Box 3)
    Featuring Music Selections, Celebrities, Vaudeville performances, News Weekly, a speech introducing Vitaphone and the feature, "The Wrong Mr. Wright" with Jean Hersholt and Enid Bennett. Dated via coverage in the Brooklyn Daily Eagle.
  - Bolero, April 7-10, [c. 1934] (Box 3)
    Vaudeville. Films: "Bolero" with George Raft, Carole Lombard; "Frontier Marshal" with George O'Brien; "4 Frightened People" with Claudette Colbert; "Jimmy and Sally" with James Dunn; George Hill and his Music Masters and Fox News.
- TNF Theatre
  - Various films, November 26 - December 1, [1917] (Box 3)
    "The Lottery Man," "Seven Keys to Baldpate," "The Silent Master," "Little Miss Optimist" and more.
- Trocadero Arch Theatre
  - Mirthful Mishaps, August 20, 1900 (Box 3)
    Broadway Girls Burlesquers in the one-act comedy, "Mirthful Mishaps," by Chas. H. Clark. Vaudeville Acts by: Allen and Allen; Clark and Emmons; Russell and Richards; Smith and Cross; Powers and Hyde; the burlesque "The King of Walla-Walla," and more.
- Unique Theatre
  - A Yiddisher Christening, January 20, 1902 (Box 3)
    Harry M. Sweeney and Orchestra. W.B. Watson's American Burlesquers in "A Yiddisher Christening" by W.B. Watson. Vaudeville Acts by: Brothers Lassard; Hawthorne and Allen; Mickey Finn; Ella Shields; Miss Belle Gordon; and more.
  - The Two Strangers, March 23, 1903 (Box 3)
    Harry M. Sweeney and Orchestra.The Famous Fay Foster Extravaganza Co. Performances: "The Two Strangers;" Nice and Coy; Scott, Bryant and Milton; Fanny Everett; Honan and Kearney; The Cleodras; Wyman and Gardner; "The Isle of Tobasco."
  - Life in Egypt, November 23, 1903 (Box 3)
    Harry M. Sweeney and Orchestra.The U.S. Beauties. Performances: "Life in Egypt," a burlesque; Bigger and Dreher; Leslie & Curdy; Lewis & Burnham; Effie Brooklin; Ferguson & Beeson; "The Greenpoint Law," a one scene comedy.
  - Krausmeyer in Ladysmith!, January 27, 1902 (Box 3)
    Harry M. Sweeney and Orchestra. Watson's Orientals. Vaudeville Acts: "Krausmeyer in Ladysmith!" by W. B. Watson; All Star Vaudeville Olio; Miss Kittie Clements; Brothers Lassard; Hawthorne and Allen; Mickey Finn; and more.
- United
  - The Cheat, October 22, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Cheat" with Pola Negri; "Silver Spurs" with Lester Cuneo; "Temporary Marriage" with Mildred Davis Lloyd; "The Destroying Angel" with Leah Baird; "Salomy Jane" with Jacqueline Logan; "Don't Marry For Money" with House Peters; and more.
  - The French Idol, October 29, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The French Idol" with Mae Murray; "Zero Hour" with Lester Cuneo; "Lawful Larceny" with Hope Hamilton; "Paris After Dark"; "Trapped in the Air" with Lester Cuneo; "The Eagle's Feather" with James Kirkwood; and more.
  - Strangers in the Night, November 26, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Strangers in the Night" with Enid Bennett; "Bright Lights of Broadway" with Lowell Sherman; "Sinner or Saint" with Betty Blythe; "Unblazed Trails" with Richard Hatton; "Ruggles of Red Gap" with Lois Wilson; and more.
  - Broken Hearts of Broadway, December 17, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Broken Hearts of Broadway" with Colleen Moore; "Shattered Reputations" with Johnny Walker; "In Search of a Thrill" with Viola Dana; "Held to Answer" with House Peters; "A Self Made Wife" with Ethel Grey Terry; and more.
  - The Country Kid, December 31, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Country Kid" with Wesley Barry; "The Common Law" with Corinne Griffith; "Breaking into Society" with Bull Montana; "Modern Marriage" with Francis X. Bushman; "A Wife in Name Only" with Edmund Lowe; and more.
  - Tea with a Kick, January 14, 1924 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Tea with a Kick" with Doris May; "The Secret of Storm Country" with Norma Talmadge; "The Man From New York"; "Other Men's Daughters"; "Between Two Husbands"; "Mine To Keep" with Bryant Washburn; and more.
  - Long Live the King, February 11, 1924 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Long Live the King" with Jackie Coogan; "The Spanish Dancer" with Pola Negri; "To the Ladies" with Theodore Roberts; "The Heart Bandit" with Viola Dana; "Waterfront Wolves" with Ora Carew; and more.
  - The Call of the Canyon, February 18, 1924 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Call of the Canyon" with Richard Dix; "The Temple of Venus" with Mary Philbin; "His Children's Children" with Bebe Daniels; "Our Hospitality" with Buster Keaton; and more.
  - Sherlock, Jr, July 14, 1924 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Sherlock, Jr." with Buster Keaton; The Confidence Man" with Thomas Meighan; "Under the Prison 'N'Galera'"; "The Trouble Shooter" with Tom Mix; "Leave it to Jerry" with Billie Rhodes; "Discontented Husbands" with James Kirkwood; and more.
- [Various venues]
  - Neighborhood Movie Guide, October 1-8, [1942] (Box 3)
    Neighborhood Movie Guide for the Rainbow, Commodore, Meserole, Alba and Marcy Theatres. Showing: "Mrs. Miniver"; "Magnificent Ambersons"; "Tin Pan Alley"; "Second Fiddle"; and more.
- [Venue unknown]
  - The First Born, Undated (Box 3)
    "The First Born" by Francis Powers. With Gertrude Tidball, Adele LeClaire, Ysobel Haskins, Logan Paul et al.
  - Paradise Alley, Undated (Box 3)
    Cast list for "Third Picture -- Paradise Alley" and "Fourth Picture -- Autumn Scene in Bronx Park."
  - [Various performances], Undated (Box 3)
    Partial list of Vaudeville acts: The Randalles, contortionists; Chas. R. Sweet; Watson & Hutchings and Ed Edwards in "The Dramatic Angel"; Canfield and Carlton; McIntyre and Heath.
- Washington
  - Love's Masquerade, July 24, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Love's Masquerade" with Conway Tearle; "A Prince There Was" with Thomas Meighan; "Nancy From Nowhere" with Bebe Daniels; "One Arabian Night" with Pola Negri; "Silver Spurs" with Lester Cuneo; and more.
  - Don't Write Letters [2 copies], July 31 ,1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Don't Write Letters" with Gareth Hughes; "Miss Lulu Bett" with Lois Wilson; "Bits of Life"; "Across the Divide" with Rosemary Theby; "Trimmed" with Hoot Gibson; "The Call of the North" with Jack Holt; and more.
  - The Miracle Man, August 7, 1922 (Box 3)